Guide to Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art special events records, 1891-2010 COR0003.4.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Musical Evening Series (MES) records, Circa 1980 - 1996; Series 17
  - After Event Reports, 1992-1994; Series 17 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Pre-Event Report, 1993; Series 17 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Pre-Event Report, 1993; Series 17 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - NEA Music Grant, 1994; Series 17 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - MES: Programs, 1983-1997; Series 17 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Recent Calendars, 1991-1993; Series 17 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Pre-Event Reports, 1995; Series 17 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Pre-Event Reports, 1995; Series 17 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Pre-Event Reports, 1994; Series 17 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Pre-Event Reports, 1994; Series 17 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - MES - Orion String Quartet, 1996 April 12; Series 17 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - MES: Loose, Circa 1991-1996; Series 17 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - MES: Raphael Ensemble, 1995 October 20; Series 17 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - MES: Angeles Quartet, 1996 March 22; Series 17 (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - MES: The Eroica Trio, 1996 January 19; Series 17 (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - MES: St. Lawrence Quartet, 1995 November 10; Series 17 (Box 62, Folder 24)
- Lectures [legacy series], 1964-1981; Series 5
  This series contains information on the Corcoran lecture group and includes correspondence, press releases, interoffice memos, planning notes, invitations to speak, and invitations to attend.
  - Standard Procedure for Lectures, Undated; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 19)
  - Schmutzhart Lecture, 1964 December 8; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 20)
  - Art USA Curator Lectures, 1965 January 5; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 21)
  - John Warnicke Lecture, 1965 January 8; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 22)
  - Chieffo Lecture, 1965 January 21; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 23)
  - Teruo Hara Lecture, 1965 February 14; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 24)
  - Jack Perlmutter Lecture, 1965 March 12; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 25)
  - Lecture Series, 1965-1966; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 26)
  - Lecture Series, 1966-1967; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 27)
  - Administration/Minutes, 1973-1979; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 28)
  - General Correspondence, 1974-1976, 1979; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 29)
  - Adminsitration/Minutes Notices, 1974-1980; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 30)
  - Barbara Novak, 1974 March 1; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 31)
  - The 1930's, 1974 March 19; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 32)
  - Contract/Lisner Auditorium, Ansel Adams Lecture, 1974 November 17; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 33)
  - Administration/In-House Memos, 1975-1976, 1979; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 34)
  - Finances/Income-Expenses, 1975-1976; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 35)
  - Finances, 1975-1978; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 36)
  - Finances/Income-Expenses, 1976-1977; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 37)
  - Metropolitan Club, 1976-1977; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 38)
  - Administration/Suggestions for Speakers, 1976-1978; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 39)
  - Applications to Perform, 1976-1978; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 40)
  - Membership Attendance, 1976-1978; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 41)
  - Membership Lists, 1978-1979; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 42)
  - Susan Alsop, Marietta Tree, 1976 January 12; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 43)
  - Mary Hemingway, 1976 January 17; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 44)
  - Poetry & Visual Arts Project, 1976 February-December; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 45)
  - Allen Ginsberg and William Burroughs, 1976 February 9; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 46)
  - Robert Wilson, 1976 April 14; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence/Mary Swift, 1976 April 15-May 1; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 48)
  - Averell Harriman-Elie Abel, 1976 May 10; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 49)
  - Poetry Award, 1976 December 8; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 50)
  - John Figueroa, 1976 December 8; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 51)
  - Lecture Committee Luncheon/William Warner, 1977 May 5; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 52)
  - Gen. Vernon Walters, 1978 February 27; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 53)
  - Contract/Albert Maysles & Films, 1978 March 3; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 54)
  - Harold Rome, 1978 April 10; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 55)
  - Albert Maysles, 1978 May 15; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 56)
  - Barbara Tuckman, 1979 April 23; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 57)
  - Amiri Baraka, 1979 May 15; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 58)
  - Kermit Roosevelt, 1979 October 1; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 59)
  - Corcoran Lecture Committee, 1980-1981; Series 5 (Box 112, Folder 60)
- Washington Art Group [legacy series], 1974-1979; Series 6
  Organized into 5 subseries: Administration, Membership, Finances, Miscellaneous, and Programs.
  - Administration, Circa 1970-1980; Series 6 Subseries 1
    This subseries contains correspondence with Trustees, memos, lists, form letters, invitations to speak, lists of suggested speakers, reports, program announcements, duty/planning checklists, requests for services.
    - Reactivation: Memos/Lists, 1979; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 112, Folder 61)
    - Reactivation: Form Letters, 1979; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 112, Folder 62)
    - Correspondence with Trustees, 1974-1975; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 112, Folder 63)
    - Invitations to Speak, 1975-1976; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 112, Folder 64)
    - Suggested Speakers, 1975-1979; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 112, Folder 65)
    - Report Sherry Ellman, 1977 June; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 112, Folder 66)
    - Report, 1975 February 28; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 112, Folder 67)
    - Annual Report, 1974-1975; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 112, Folder 68)
    - Program Announcements, Undated; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 112, Folder 69)
    - Programs; Memos and Checklists, 1974-1980; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 112, Folder 70)
    - Program Procedures (undated), Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 112, Folder 71)
    - Programs; Requests for Services, Undated; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 112, Folder 72)
    - Form Letters, 1974; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 112, Folder 73)
  - Membership, 1974-1980; Series 6 Subseries 2
    This subseries contains correspondence, complementary and corporate guest lists, prospects, invitations to join, membership lists, renewal lists.
    - Correspondence, 1974-1980; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 74)
    - Complementary & Corporate, 1977; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 75)
    - Attendance List, 1979-1980; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 76)
    - Prospects, 1978; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 77)
    - Prospects, 1977; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 78)
    - Prospects, 1974; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 79)
    - Invitations to Join, 1979; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 80)
    - Invitations to Join, 1977; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 81)
    - Invitations to Join, 1976; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 82)
    - Invitations to Join, 1975; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 83)
    - Invitations to Join, 1974; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 84)
    - List, 1977-1978; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 85)
    - Lists, 1974-1975; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 86)
    - Renewal List, 1977; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 87)
    - Renewal Lists, 1975; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 88)
    - Renewals, 1976-1977; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 89)
    - Attendance Reports, 1974-1978; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 90)
    - Receipts, 1976-1978; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 112, Folder 91)
  - Finances, 1974-1980; Series 6 Subseries 3
    This subseries contains statements, reports on income and expenses.
    - Statements and Reports, 1980-1981; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 112, Folder 92)
    - Statements and Reports, 1979-1980; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 112, Folder 93)
    - Statements and Reports, 1977-1978; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 112, Folder 94)
    - Statements and Reports, 1976-1977; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 112, Folder 95)
    - Statements and Reports, 1975-1976; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 112, Folder 96)
    - Statements and Reports, 1974-1975; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 112, Folder 97)
    - Income, 1974-1977; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 112, Folder 98)
    - Expenses, 1974-1977; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 112, Folder 99)
  - Miscellaneous, Circa 1970-1980; Series 6 Subseries 4
    This subseries contains taxes, updated lists.
    - Miscellaneous, Undated; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 112, Folder 100)
    - Taxes, 1974; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 112, Folder 101)
    - Lists, Undated; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 112, Folder 102)
  - Programs, 1974-1980; Series 6 Subseries 5
    This subseries contains information on the program participants, includes memos, correspondence, menus, attendance records.
    - Friedensreich Hundertwasser, 1980 November 17; Series 6 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 103)
    - Friedensreich Hundertwasser Folder # Reservations, 1980 November 17; Series 6 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 104)
    - Bruce Davidson, 1980 March 31; Series 6 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 105)
    - Yehudi Menuhin, 1980 March 17; Series 6 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 106)
    - Ozzie Davis Luncheon Lecture, 1984 February 4; Series 6 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 107)
    - Andy Warhol, 1979 November 14; Series 6 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 108)
    - Wendell Garrett, 1979 October 19; Series 6 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 109)
    - Paul Elicker, 1977 February 27; Series 6 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 110)
    - Duane Hanson, 1977 December 12; Series 6 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 111)
    - Joshua C. Taylor, 1977 November 7; Series 6 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 112)
    - Fred Richmond, 1977 October 3; Series 6 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 113)
    - John Brademas, 1977 June 20; Series 6 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 114)
    - Jane Livingston, 1977 May 2; Series 6 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 115)
    - Lowell Nesbit, 1976 May 24; Series 6 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 116)
    - Sir Norman Reid, 1976 May 3; Series 6 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 117)
    - Marchal E. Landgren, 1976 February 9; Series 6 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 118)
    - J. Carter Brown, 1975 December 15; Series 6 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 119)
    - Andre Emmerich, 1975 November 10; Series 6 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 120)
    - Hilton Kramer, 1975 September 29; Series 6 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 121)
    - Perry T. Rathbone, 1975 May 5; Series 6 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 122)
    - Gene Davis, 1975 March 17; Series 6 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 123)
    - Nancy Hanks, 1975 January 13; Series 6 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 124)
    - James Biddle, 1974 November 11; Series 6 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 125)
    - Helen Frankenthaler, 1974 October 7; Series 6 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 126)
    - Tokyo String Quartet, 1974 June 18; Series 6 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 127)
    - Thomas Hoving, 1974 April 29; Series 6 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 128)
    - Frank Getlein, 1974 February 25; Series 6 Subseries 5 (Box 112, Folder 129)
- Administration [legacy series], 1960-1984; Series 7
  Separated Materials
  This series contains the administrative records created by the Special Events Office.
  Organized into six subseries: Correspondence, Events, Finance, Volunteers, Personnel, and Miscellaneous
  - Correspondence, 1960-1983; Series 7 Subseries 1
    Arranged chronologically by month within years. Original order was maintained in order to show a progression of events and responses.
    This subseries contains general correspondence.
    - Correspondence, 1960 April, September-December; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 113, Folders 1-5)
    - Correspondence, 1961 January-December; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 113, Folders 6-12)
    - Correspondence, 1962 January-December; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 113, Folders 13-20)
    - Correspondence, 1963 February-December; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 113, Folders 21-31)
    - Correspondence, 1964 January-October; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 113, Folders 32-37)
    - Correspondence, 1965 January-December; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 113, Folders 38-45)
    - Correspondence, 1966 January-March, November; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 113, Folders 46-49)
    - Correspondence, 1967 February, September-December; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 113, Folders 50-54)
    - Correspondence, 1968 May; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 113, Folder 55)
    - Correspondence, 1969 February, May, July-August; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 113, Folders 56-59)
    - Correspondence, 1970 August; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 113, Folder 60)
    - Correspondence, 1972 July; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 113, Folder 61)
    - Correspondence, 1973 November; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 113, Folder 62)
    - Correspondence, 1974 June-August, October-December; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 113, Folders 63-68)
    - Correspondence, 1975 January-September, November-December; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 113, Folders 69-79)
    - Correspondence, 1976 January-May, July; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 113, Folders 80-85)
    - Correspondence, 1981 January-February, June-December; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 113, Folders 86-93)
    - Correspondence, 1982; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 113, Folders 94-105)
    - Correspondence, 1983 January-August; Series 7 Subseries 1 (Box 113, Folders 106-113)
  - Events, 1970-1984; Series 7 Subseries 2
    Arranged chronologically by month within years.
    This subseries contains day-to-day planning in operation of the Special Events Office. Includes bi-monthly reports, attendance reports, correspondance, inter-office memos, pre-event and post-event reports.
    - Events, 1970; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 114)
    - Events, 1971; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 115)
    - Events, 1973-1974; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 116)
    - Events, 1979; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folders 117-119)
    - Events, 1979 September-December; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folders 120-123)
    - Events, 1980 January-June, September-December; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folders 124-133)
    - Bi-Monthly Reports, 1979; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 134)
    - Events, 1982 May 1-3, June 1-3, July-September, October 1-4, November 1-2, December 1-4; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folders 1-19)
    - Events, 1983 January 1-2, February 1-3, March 1-3, April 1-4, May 1-3; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folders 20-34)
    - Bi-Monthly Reports, 1980; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 35)
    - Bi-Monthly Reports, 1981; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 36)
    - Events, 1982 January-April; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folders 37-40)
    - Events, 1983 June; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 41)
    - Events, 1983 August; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Attendance Reports, 1983-1984; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Events, 1983 July; Series 7 Subseries 2 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Finance, 1969-1982; Series 7 Subseries 3
    Contains financial information that is primarily comprised of musical events budgets with some planning and projected planning.
    - Music, 1969-1971, 1975-1976; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 115, Folders 4-6)
    - Contribution Requests, 1975-1976; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Events Planning Budget, 1975-1976; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Music, 1976-1978; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 115, Folders 9-10)
    - Musical Events Budgets, 1977-1978; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - Music, 1980-1982; Series 7 Subseries 3 (Box 115, Folders 12-13)
  - Volunteers, 1965-1979; Series 7 Subseries 4
    This subseries contains correspondence, planning and coordinating information on volunteers, justification of and need for volunteer help -- "The Gift of Time".
    - Summer Applications, 1965; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 115, Folders 14-15)
    - Volunteers, 1975; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 115, Folder 16)
    - Volunteers, 1976; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 115, Folders 17-18)
    - Volunteers, 1977; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 115, Folder 19)
    - Volunteers, 1978; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 115, Folder 20)
    - Volunteers, 1979; Series 7 Subseries 4 (Box 115, Folder 21)
  - Personnel, 1965-1967; Series 7 Subseries 5
    - Personnel, 1965; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 115, Folders 22-24)
    - Personnel, 1966; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 115, Folders 25-26)
    - Personnel, 1967; Series 7 Subseries 5 (Box 115, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous, 1952-1984; Series 7 Subseries 6
    This subseries contains incomplete committee minutes and records, facility use prospects and facility use inquires telephone log -- also Toyota commericial production.
    - Weekend Duty Report, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 6 (Box 115, Folder 28)
    - Auditorium/Piano, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 6 (Box 115, Folder 29)
    - Music Advisory Committee, 1952-1979; Series 7 Subseries 6 (Box 115, Folder 30)
    - Music Committee, 1964-1967; Series 7 Subseries 6 (Box 115, Folders 31-34)
    - Special Events Committee, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 6 (Box 115, Folder 35)
    - Special Events Committee, 1978-1980; Series 7 Subseries 6 (Box 115, Folder 36)
    - Facility Use-Telephone Inquiries Log Book, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 6 (Box 115, Folder 37)
    - Facility Use Prospects, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 6 (Box 115, Folders 38-40)
    - Interoffice Memos-Roy Slade & Sherry Ellman, 1974-1975; Series 7 Subseries 6 (Box 115, Folder 41)
    - Outside Groups-Procedures For Use of Corcoran Facility, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 6 (Box 115, Folder 42)
    - Press Release Schedule, Undated; Series 7 Subseries 6 (Box 115, Folder 43)
    - Toyota Commercial Productions, 1980 February 3; Series 7 Subseries 6 (Box 115, Folder 44)
- Administrative files, Circa 1978-2000; Series 11
  This series contains records that detail the work of the Corcoran Gallery of Art special events division of the Corcoran Gallery of Art. These records date primarily from 1978 - 2000.
  - Forms for Personality File, Circa 1990-1999; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Corporate Collections, 1988; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Personalities A, 1984-1989; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Michael Botwinick, 1982-1987; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Personalities B, 1984-1989; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Personalities C, 1984-1986; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Personalities D, 1982-1985; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Cafritz, Circa 1990-1999; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Personalities E, 1982-1987; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Personalities F, 1982-1989; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Personalities G, 1982-1989; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Personalities H, 1982-1989; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Hammer, Armand, 1978-1985; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Personalities I, 1984-1985; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Personalities J, 1983-1988; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Trustee Freeborn G. Jewett, Jr., 1988; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Personalities K, 1983-1987; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Kreeger, 1988-1989; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Personalities L, 1983-1987; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Jane Livingston, 1988; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Personalities M, 1984-1991; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Personalities N, 1985-1986; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Personalities O, 1983-1985; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Christina Orr-Cahall, Director, Circa 1990-1999; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Elizabeth C. Punsalan Hep-Cat #1, 1988; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Personalities P, 1982-1987; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Personalities Q, 1988; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Personalities R, 1980-1988; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Personalities S, 1984-1988; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Personalities T, 1983-1988; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Personalities U, 1984; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Personalities W, 1982-1987; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Personalities X,Y, Z, 1982-1987; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Legal Counsel Nicholas Ward, Circa 1990-1999; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Past Director's of the CGA, Circa 1990-1999; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Top Collectors, Circa 1990-1999; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Jay "Talkin' and Drinkin'" Stuckey, Circa 1990-1999; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - News Articles, Circa 1990-1999; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Special Events News Clippings, Circa 1990-1999; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Personalities V, 1982-1987; Series 11 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence, 1988 December; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1988 October; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1988 September; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1988 August; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1988 July; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1988 June; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1988 May; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1988 April; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1988 March; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1988 February; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1988 January; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1987 December; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1987 November; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1987 October; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1987 September; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1987 August; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 1987 July; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 1987 June; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1987 May; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1987 April; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1987 March; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1987 March; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 1987 February; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, 1987 January; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, 1986 December; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, 1986 November; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, 1986 October; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, 1986 September; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, 1986 August; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, 1986 July; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, 1986 June; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, 1986 May; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, 1986 April; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, 1986 March; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, 1986 February; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, 1986 January; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, 1985 December; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, 1985 November; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence, 1985 October; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence, 1985 September; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence, 1985 August; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence, 1985 July; Series 11 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence, June 1985; Series 11 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1985 May; Series 11 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1985 April; Series 11 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1985 March; Series 11 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1985 February; Series 11 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1985 January; Series 11 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1984 December; Series 11 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1984 November; Series 11 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1984 October; Series 11 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1984 September; Series 11 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1984 August; Series 11 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1984 July; Series 11 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Cleveland Quartet, 1986 October 10; Series 11 (Box 20, Folder 13)